<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>celebrity net worth &#8211; Celleb News</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/celebrity-net-worth/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 15:41:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Jared Leto Net Worth: A Look at the Multifaceted Stars Wealth</title>
		<link>/jared-leto-net-worth.html</link>
					<comments>/jared-leto-net-worth.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 15:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Celebrity Net Worth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[actor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[business ventures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celebrity net worth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[investments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jared Leto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[musician]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[net worth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thirty Seconds to Mars]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/jared-leto-net-worth.html</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jared leto net worth &#8211; Jared Leto&#8217;s net worth is a testament to his extraordinary talent and unwavering dedication across multiple creative fields. He&#8217;s not just an actor, he&#8217;s a... ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> <strong>Jared leto net worth</strong> &#8211; Jared Leto&#8217;s net worth is a testament to his extraordinary talent and unwavering dedication across multiple creative fields.  He&#8217;s not just an actor, he&#8217;s a musician, a producer, and a philanthropist, each facet contributing to his financial success. From his iconic roles in films like &#8220;Dallas Buyers Club&#8221; and &#8220;Suicide Squad&#8221; to his Grammy-winning work as the frontman of Thirty Seconds to Mars, Leto has consistently captivated audiences and amassed a fortune along the way.</p>
<p>This exploration delves into the intricacies of Jared Leto&#8217;s net worth, examining the factors that have shaped his financial journey.  We&#8217;ll analyze his career milestones, strategic investments, and lifestyle choices, uncovering the secrets behind his remarkable wealth. </p>
<h2>Jared Leto&#8217;s Career and Earnings</h2>
<p>Jared Leto, a multi-talented artist known for his roles in film, music, and directing, has built a remarkable career spanning over three decades. His diverse skill set and unwavering dedication have propelled him to the forefront of his respective industries, resulting in a substantial net worth.</p>
<p>This section delves into the evolution of his career, highlighting major projects and their impact on his financial success. </p>
<h3>Jared Leto&#8217;s Early Career and Music Earnings</h3>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s journey began with his involvement in the music industry. In 1988, he co-founded the band 30 Seconds to Mars, which quickly gained recognition for its alternative rock sound and theatrical performances. The band&#8217;s debut album, &#8220;30 Seconds to Mars,&#8221; released in 2002, achieved commercial success, earning a platinum certification in the United States.</p>
<p>Their subsequent albums, &#8220;A Beautiful Lie&#8221; (2005), &#8220;This Is War&#8221; (2009), &#8220;Love, Lust, Faith and Dreams&#8221; (2013), and &#8220;America&#8221; (2018), further solidified their position in the music industry. While it is difficult to pinpoint exact earnings from each album, the band&#8217;s global tours and extensive merchandise sales contributed significantly to Leto&#8217;s wealth.</p>
<h3>Jared Leto&#8217;s Acting Career and Film Earnings</h3>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s acting career took off in the early 1990s with roles in films like &#8220;My So-Called Life&#8221; (1994) and &#8220;Prefontaine&#8221; (1997). However, it was his performance as a transgender woman in the 2000 film &#8220;Requiem for a Dream&#8221; that garnered critical acclaim and established him as a serious actor.</p>
<p>His subsequent roles in films like &#8220;Panic Room&#8221; (2002), &#8220;Alexander&#8221; (2004), and &#8220;Lord of War&#8221; (2005) further showcased his versatility and talent. In 2013, Leto&#8217;s portrayal of the Joker in &#8220;Suicide Squad&#8221; earned him widespread recognition and an Academy Award nomination.</p>
<p>The film&#8217;s box office success, generating over $745 million worldwide, contributed significantly to his earnings. </p>
<h3>Jared Leto&#8217;s Directorial Debut and Other Ventures</h3>
<p>Beyond his music and acting endeavors, Jared Leto has also ventured into directing. His directorial debut, &#8220;Chapter 27&#8221; (2007), a biographical film about the murder of John Lennon, garnered mixed reviews. The film&#8217;s budget of $10 million and limited box office success did not generate substantial revenue for Leto.</p>
<p>However, his other ventures, including endorsements and investments, have contributed to his overall wealth. </p>
<h3>Jared Leto&#8217;s Estimated Net Worth</h3>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s net worth is estimated to be around $80 million. This figure is based on his earnings from music, acting, directing, and other ventures. While exact figures are not publicly available, it is clear that his successful career across multiple industries has made him one of the wealthiest entertainers in the world.</p>
<h2>Investments and Business Ventures</h2>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-71212" src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Jared-Leto-House-of-Gucci-UK-premiere-2021.jpg" width="700" height="526" alt="Jared leto net worth" title="Leto" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Jared-Leto-House-of-Gucci-UK-premiere-2021.jpg 700w, /wp-content/uploads/2024/08/Jared-Leto-House-of-Gucci-UK-premiere-2021-300x225.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></p>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s success extends beyond his acting and musical endeavors. He is a savvy investor with a keen eye for promising ventures, further bolstering his wealth. He has a diverse portfolio that includes investments in technology, real estate, and various other industries.</p>
<h3>Tequila Honcho</h3>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s investment in Tequila Honcho, a high-end tequila brand, highlights his commitment to quality and luxury. He is a partner in the company, which is known for its handcrafted, small-batch tequila. His involvement has helped elevate the brand&#8217;s profile and expand its reach, contributing to its success and his own financial gain.</p>
<p>Tequila Honcho&#8217;s premium positioning aligns with Leto&#8217;s own brand image, showcasing his discerning taste and business acumen. </p>
<h3>Investment Strategies</h3>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s investment strategy is characterized by a focus on emerging technologies, innovative companies, and ventures with high growth potential. He often invests in companies at their early stages, recognizing the potential for significant returns. His approach involves careful due diligence, understanding the market trends, and identifying companies with strong leadership and a compelling vision.</p>
<h2>Lifestyle and Expenses: Jared Leto Net Worth</h2>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s lifestyle is a reflection of his success in the entertainment industry. His extravagant spending habits and meticulous attention to detail contribute to his public image and personal brand. However, his financial choices also impact his overall net worth, highlighting the importance of balance between indulgence and responsible financial management.</p>
<h3>Home, Jared leto net worth</h3>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s home is a testament to his wealth and sophisticated taste. He owns a luxurious penthouse apartment in New York City&#8217;s Tribeca neighborhood. This sprawling residence offers breathtaking views of the city skyline and boasts high-end amenities such as a private elevator, a rooftop terrace, and a state-of-the-art home theater.</p>
<p>The estimated value of this property is over $30 million, representing a significant portion of his overall wealth. </p>
<h3>Transportation</h3>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s transportation choices are a blend of practicality and luxury. He owns a fleet of high-performance vehicles, including a Tesla Model S, a Mercedes-Benz S-Class, and a vintage Cadillac. These vehicles provide him with both comfort and convenience, allowing him to navigate the bustling city streets and travel comfortably for work commitments.</p>
<p>While these vehicles are expensive, they also represent a substantial investment, potentially appreciating in value over time. </p>
<h3>Personal Expenditures</h3>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s personal expenditures are known to be lavish. He enjoys fine dining, luxurious travel, and exclusive experiences. His wardrobe is filled with designer clothing and accessories, and he is known for his meticulous attention to detail in his personal style.</p>
<p>These expenditures contribute to his high profile and enhance his public image, but they also represent a significant drain on his overall net worth. </p>
<h3>Charitable Contributions</h3>
<p>Despite his extravagant lifestyle, Jared Leto is also known for his charitable contributions. He is a vocal advocate for various causes, including environmental conservation, animal welfare, and LGBTQ+ rights. He has donated to organizations such as the American Civil Liberties Union, the Sierra Club, and the Humane Society.</p>
<p>His philanthropic activities demonstrate his commitment to social responsibility and highlight the importance of giving back to the community. </p>
<h2>Question Bank</h2>
<p><strong>How did Jared Leto make his fortune?</strong></p>
<p>Jared Leto&#8217;s wealth stems from his successful acting career, music career with Thirty Seconds to Mars, and strategic investments in various businesses. </p>
<p><strong>What are some of Jared Leto&#8217;s notable investments?</strong></p>
<p>He has invested in companies like Tequila honcho, demonstrating his keen eye for business opportunities. </p>
<p><strong>Does Jared Leto donate to charity?</strong></p>
<p>Yes, Jared Leto is known for his philanthropic endeavors, supporting various causes through his charitable contributions. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/jared-leto-net-worth.html/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>George Lopez Net Worth: A Look at His Career and Finances</title>
		<link>/george-lopez-net-worth.html</link>
					<comments>/george-lopez-net-worth.html#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 15:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Celebrity Net Worth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[actor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[celebrity net worth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comedian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[george lopez]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[net worth]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/george-lopez-net-worth.html</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[George Lopez net worth is a testament to his comedic brilliance and entrepreneurial spirit. From humble beginnings to becoming a household name, Lopez&#8217;s journey is marked by laughter, resilience, and... ]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>George Lopez net worth is a testament to his comedic brilliance and entrepreneurial spirit. From humble beginnings to becoming a household name, Lopez&#8217;s journey is marked by laughter, resilience, and a strong work ethic. His journey is a story of how talent, hard work, and a touch of luck can lead to incredible success.</p>
<p>This exploration dives into the various facets of George Lopez&#8217;s financial success, examining his career milestones, income sources, and the factors that have shaped his net worth. We&#8217;ll explore how his comedic style, business ventures, and cultural background have contributed to his remarkable achievements.</p>
<h2>George Lopez&#8217;s Career and Earnings</h2>
<p>George Lopez, a comedic powerhouse, has carved a remarkable career spanning decades, leaving an indelible mark on the entertainment industry. His journey, marked by resilience and a sharp wit, has propelled him to immense success, making him a household name and a financial powerhouse.</p>
<h3>George Lopez&#8217;s Career Timeline</h3>
<p>The trajectory of George Lopez&#8217;s career is a testament to his talent and determination. His journey, punctuated by pivotal moments, highlights the evolution of his comedic genius and his unwavering commitment to his craft. </p>
<ul>
<li><b>Early Career (1980s-1990s):</b>George Lopez&#8217;s comedic journey began in the late 1980s, where he honed his craft in stand-up comedy clubs across the country. His early years were marked by a relentless pursuit of success, performing in diverse venues, from small clubs to larger stages.</p>
<p>This period laid the foundation for his unique brand of humor, characterized by observational wit, social commentary, and relatable experiences. </li>
<li><b>Breakthrough and Recognition (2000s):</b>The turn of the millennium marked a significant turning point in George Lopez&#8217;s career. He achieved national recognition with his self-titled sitcom, &#8220;George Lopez,&#8221; which aired on ABC from 2002 to 2007. The show, a critical and commercial success, garnered numerous accolades and solidified his position as a leading figure in television comedy.</p>
<p>It centered on a working-class Mexican-American family, offering a fresh perspective on family dynamics and cultural nuances, resonating with a wide audience. </li>
<li><b>Diversification and Continued Success (2010s-Present):</b>Following the success of his sitcom, George Lopez continued to diversify his career, venturing into film, television, and stand-up comedy. He appeared in movies like &#8220;Beverly Hills Chihuahua&#8221; and &#8220;The Smurfs,&#8221; and hosted various television specials and events. His stand-up comedy tours, which continued to draw massive crowds, showcased his evolving comedic style, marked by sharp social commentary and personal anecdotes.</p>
<p> He also continued to produce and develop projects for television and film, further expanding his creative reach and influence. </li>
</ul>
<h3>Evolution of George Lopez&#8217;s Comedic Style</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s comedic style is a unique blend of observational humor, social commentary, and personal anecdotes. His ability to find humor in everyday situations, coupled with his sharp wit and relatable experiences, has resonated with audiences across generations and cultural backgrounds.</p>
<ul>
<li><b>Observational Humor:</b>George Lopez excels at finding humor in the ordinary, drawing inspiration from everyday experiences and social interactions. His comedic observations, often tinged with a touch of irony, highlight the absurdities and contradictions of life, making his material both relatable and insightful.</p>
</li>
<li><b>Social Commentary:</b>George Lopez&#8217;s comedy is not just about laughter; it also serves as a platform for social commentary. He uses his humor to address societal issues, including race, class, and cultural differences, offering a fresh perspective and sparking important conversations. His comedic voice often challenges stereotypes and preconceived notions, promoting understanding and empathy.</p>
</li>
<li><b>Personal Anecdotes:</b>George Lopez&#8217;s comedic persona is deeply rooted in his personal experiences. He weaves his life stories, struggles, and triumphs into his routines, creating a sense of intimacy and authenticity that connects him with his audience. His personal anecdotes, often infused with humor and self-deprecation, offer a glimpse into his life and resonate with viewers who relate to his struggles and triumphs.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>George Lopez&#8217;s Business Ventures and Investments</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s success extends beyond his comedic talent; he is also a shrewd businessman with a keen eye for opportunity. His entrepreneurial ventures have diversified his income streams and cemented his financial success. </p>
<ul>
<li><b>Television Production:</b>George Lopez&#8217;s involvement in television production has been a significant contributor to his net worth. His production company, Lopez Entertainment, has produced numerous television shows, including his self-titled sitcom, &#8220;George Lopez,&#8221; and &#8220;Lopez Tonight,&#8221; a late-night talk show. His production ventures have allowed him to control his creative vision and generate significant revenue.</p>
</li>
<li><b>Stand-up Comedy:</b>George Lopez&#8217;s stand-up comedy tours continue to be a major source of income. His live performances draw massive crowds, generating substantial revenue from ticket sales, merchandise, and other related ventures. His ability to connect with audiences through his humor and relatable experiences has made his stand-up comedy a consistent source of financial success.</p>
</li>
<li><b>Other Ventures:</b>George Lopez&#8217;s business ventures extend beyond television and stand-up comedy. He has invested in various other projects, including a tequila brand and a clothing line, further diversifying his income streams and expanding his brand. His business acumen has allowed him to leverage his popularity and brand recognition to create successful ventures.</p>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>Impact of Cultural Background and Experiences</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s cultural background and experiences have played a pivotal role in shaping his comedic voice and contributing to his success. His Mexican-American heritage has provided him with a unique perspective on life, culture, and society. </p>
<ul>
<li><b>Representation and Inclusivity:</b>George Lopez&#8217;s success as a Mexican-American comedian has been instrumental in promoting representation and inclusivity in the entertainment industry. His comedic voice has given a platform to the experiences of a marginalized community, challenging stereotypes and fostering understanding. His success has inspired other artists from diverse backgrounds to pursue their dreams, paving the way for greater representation and diversity in entertainment.</p>
</li>
<li><b>Relatable Experiences:</b>George Lopez&#8217;s personal experiences, shaped by his cultural background and upbringing, resonate deeply with a diverse audience. His comedic observations about family, culture, and social issues connect with viewers who relate to his struggles, triumphs, and the complexities of navigating cultural identity.</p>
<p>His ability to draw humor from his personal experiences has made him a relatable and beloved figure, expanding his appeal beyond a specific demographic. </li>
<li><b>Cultural Impact:</b>George Lopez&#8217;s comedic voice has had a profound cultural impact, challenging societal norms and promoting understanding and empathy. His humor, often infused with social commentary, has sparked conversations about race, class, and cultural differences, encouraging audiences to view the world from different perspectives.</p>
<p>His influence extends beyond entertainment, contributing to a broader cultural dialogue about identity, representation, and inclusion. </li>
</ul>
<h2>Income Sources and Revenue Streams</h2>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-71206" src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/e9df0d1803f93b208733725f0ffaff51-1.jpg" width="700" height="393" alt="George lopez net worth" title="George grandmother" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/e9df0d1803f93b208733725f0ffaff51-1.jpg 700w, /wp-content/uploads/2024/08/e9df0d1803f93b208733725f0ffaff51-1-300x168.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2024/08/e9df0d1803f93b208733725f0ffaff51-1-355x199.jpg 355w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></p>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s wealth is a testament to his multifaceted career, spanning television, stand-up comedy, film, and other ventures. His income streams are diverse, reflecting his ability to connect with audiences across various platforms. </p>
<h3>Television Shows</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s most significant revenue source has been his television career. His eponymous sitcom, &#8220;George Lopez,&#8221; which aired from 2002 to 2007, was a critical and commercial success, earning him a substantial salary and syndication royalties. The show&#8217;s popularity led to various spin-offs and specials, further contributing to his earnings.</p>
<h3>Stand-up Comedy Tours</h3>
<p>Stand-up comedy remains a core element of George Lopez&#8217;s career. His live performances generate significant income through ticket sales, merchandise, and sponsorships. His comedic talent and engaging stage presence have consistently drawn large crowds, ensuring a steady flow of revenue from his tours.</p>
<h3>Endorsements</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s widespread appeal and recognizable brand have attracted numerous endorsement deals. He has partnered with companies across various sectors, including automotive, food, and beverages. These endorsements generate income through fees and royalties, adding to his overall wealth. </p>
<h3>Merchandise Sales</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s loyal fanbase has fueled a thriving merchandise market. His name and image appear on a range of products, including clothing, accessories, and home goods. Sales from these merchandise items contribute to his income, reflecting the enduring popularity of his brand.</p>
<h3>Royalties</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s intellectual property, including his comedy routines, television shows, and other creative works, generates ongoing royalty income. These royalties are paid out whenever his work is used or distributed, providing a consistent revenue stream. </p>
<h3>Other Projects, George lopez net worth</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s entrepreneurial spirit has led him to invest in various ventures beyond his core entertainment career. These include real estate investments, business ventures, and other projects that generate income and contribute to his overall net worth. </p>
<h3>Financial Impact</h3>
<p>The financial impact of George Lopez&#8217;s various ventures is significant. His television shows, stand-up comedy tours, and endorsements have been particularly profitable, generating substantial income and contributing significantly to his overall wealth. The success of his sitcom &#8220;George Lopez&#8221; has been a major driver of his earnings, with syndication royalties providing a steady stream of revenue.</p>
<h3>Contribution to Net Worth</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s diverse income streams have contributed to his impressive net worth. His television career, stand-up comedy, and endorsements have been the primary drivers of his wealth. The syndication royalties from his sitcom, &#8220;George Lopez,&#8221; and the ongoing revenue from his stand-up comedy tours have played a crucial role in building his financial success.</p>
<h2>Factors Influencing Net Worth: George Lopez Net Worth</h2>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s substantial net worth is a testament to his remarkable career in entertainment, astute business decisions, and unwavering dedication to his craft.  His journey from humble beginnings to becoming a household name is a story of hard work, resilience, and an undeniable talent that has captivated audiences worldwide.</p>
<h3>Longevity in the Entertainment Industry</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s enduring presence in the entertainment industry is a significant contributor to his wealth. His career spans decades, encompassing stand-up comedy, television, film, and radio. This sustained success has allowed him to build a substantial fan base, secure lucrative contracts, and generate consistent income streams.</p>
<h3>Business Acumen</h3>
<p>Beyond his artistic talents, George Lopez exhibits keen business acumen. He has wisely diversified his income sources, venturing into ventures beyond his core entertainment career. These ventures include production companies, restaurants, and other entrepreneurial pursuits, demonstrating his ability to capitalize on opportunities and expand his financial portfolio.</p>
<h3>Brand Recognition</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s widespread recognition as a comedian, actor, and television personality has been instrumental in building his brand value. His strong brand recognition translates into lucrative endorsement deals, sponsorship opportunities, and a loyal following that supports his various projects. </p>
<h3>Philanthropic Activities and Community Involvement</h3>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s philanthropic endeavors and active community involvement have played a crucial role in shaping his public image and fostering positive associations with his brand. His dedication to charitable causes resonates with audiences and contributes to his overall financial success by enhancing his reputation and building trust among fans.</p>
<h3>Market Trends and Economic Conditions</h3>
<p>The entertainment industry, like any other sector, is subject to market trends and economic fluctuations. George Lopez&#8217;s earnings and net worth have been influenced by factors such as the popularity of stand-up comedy, the demand for television programming, and the overall health of the economy.</p>
<p>His ability to adapt to changing trends and navigate economic cycles has been key to his sustained financial success. </p>
<h3>Estimated Value of Assets</h3>
<table>
<tr>
<th>Asset</th>
<th>Estimated Value</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Real Estate</td>
<td>$20 million</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Investments</td>
<td>$10 million</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Other Possessions</td>
<td>$5 million</td>
</tr>
</table>
<h2>FAQ Insights</h2>
<p><strong>What is George Lopez&#8217;s most famous TV show?</strong></p>
<p>George Lopez&#8217;s most famous TV show is &#8220;George Lopez,&#8221; a sitcom that aired from 2002 to 2007. It was a critical and commercial success, earning him numerous awards and accolades. </p>
<p><strong>Does George Lopez have any other businesses?</strong></p>
<p>Yes, George Lopez has several business ventures outside of entertainment, including investments in real estate, restaurants, and other ventures. </p>
<p><strong>What is George Lopez&#8217;s philanthropic work?</strong></p>
<p>George Lopez is known for his philanthropy and actively supports various charities, including those focused on education, health, and social justice. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/george-lopez-net-worth.html/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
